[MUSIC]
(音乐)
Stanford University,
斯坦福大学,
>> Okay, welcome to Stanford CS193P, Winter of 2017,
> >好的,欢迎来到斯坦福CS193P,2017年冬天,
This is Developing iOS Applications,
这是开发iOS应用程序,
this is lecture number 17, I said,
我说,这是讲座数量17日
Yes, and we have a guest lecturer today
是的,我们有今天的客座讲师
who's gonna talk to us about accessibility,
谁来和我们谈谈可访问性,
His name is Skylar Peterson,
他的名字叫Skylar彼得森,
Why don't you come up here, Skylar?
你为什么不来这里,Skylar吗?
It's all yours,
都是你的,
Thank you very much,
非常感谢你,
All righty,
好了,
Good afternoon, everybody,
大家下午好,
As he said, my name is Skylar Peterson,
他说,我的名字叫Skylar彼得森,
I am a member of Apple's Accessibility team,
我是一个苹果的可访问性小组成员,
If you don't know exactly what I mean by that,
如果你不知道我的意思,
then don't worry,
别担心,
It's what I'm here to talk to you about today,
这就是我今天来和你谈谈,
I first wanna thank Paul for
我第一次想感谢保罗
inviting us here to speak today,
邀请我们今天在这里说,
Hopefully you'll find what I have to say meaningful in some
希望你会发现我不得不说有意义一些
way, and choose to apply it to your own work in the future,
,选择把它应用到自己的工作在未来,
So before we get started,
在我们开始之前,
let me tell you just a little bit about myself,
让我告诉你一点关于我自己,
I actually graduated from Stanford in 2014,
我2014年毕业于斯坦福大学,
I studied computer science, and
我学习计算机科学,
my concentration was in HCI,
我的注意力在人机交互,
I took this class while I was here, and
我把这门课的时候,
it's actually one of the reasons that I fell in love
它实际上的原因之一,我爱上了你
with iOS as a platform and why I'm in the job I'm in today,
与iOS平台,为什么我在工作我在今天,
so thank you for that as well,
谢谢你,,
After I graduated I spent a year and a half working at
毕业后我工作了一年半
an enterprise software company called Citrix,
企业软件公司叫Citrix,
where I worked on two different iOS applications,
我工作在两个不同的iOS应用程序,
And then a little over a year ago,
然后一年多前,
I made the jump to the Accessibility team at Apple,
我跳上了可访问性团队在苹果,
where I focus mainly on iOS,
我主要关注iOS的地方,
there's a couple things that I'd like to cover with you,
有很多事情我想和你在一起,
So for today,
所以在今天,
First of all,
首先,
what exactly do we mean when we say accessibility?
我们具体指的是当我们说易访问性?
And once you understand that,
一旦你明白了,
how do you take the tools that we've created for you and
你怎么把你的工具,我们已经创建了吗
apply them to your own work to make your apps accessible?
将它们应用到自己的工作使您的应用程序访问吗?
So included in that we're gonna take a look at
中,我们会看一看
the UIAccessibility API,
UIAccessibility API,
We're gonna take a look at several vision accommodations
我们会看看一些视觉住宿
that you should consider when designing your applications,
你应该考虑在设计应用程序时,
and specifically I'm going to call out dynamic
特别是我要调用动态
type as an important feature,
类型作为一个重要的特性,
And at the end I'd like to discuss some opportunities
最后我想讨论一些机会
available to you as a developer in the accessibility
提供给你作为一个开发者的可访问性
space,
空间,
So let's get started,
所以让我们开始,
I'd like to begin with a brief video that
我想开始一个简短的视频
Apple produced towards the end of last year,
去年年底苹果生产,
[MUSIC]
(音乐)
People think that having a disability is a barrier,
人认为残疾是一个障碍,
[MUSIC],
(音乐)
But that's not the way I see it,
但这不是我看来,
It, [MUSIC]
(音乐)
You can catch up with friends,
你可以赶上朋友,
[MUSIC]
(音乐)
Ready? You can capture a moment with
准备好了吗?
your family,
你的家人,
One face, small face,
一个脸,小小的脸,
Focus log,
集中日志,
[MUSIC]
(音乐)
And you can start the day bright and early,
你可以一大早的开始一天的工作,
[MUSIC]
(音乐)
You can take a trip to somewhere new,
你可以去新的地方,
[MUSIC]
(音乐)
3 miles to the summit,
3英里的峰会上,
[MUSIC]
(音乐)
You can concentrate on every word of the story,
你可以专注于故事的每一个字,
A bird begun to sing,
鸟儿开始唱歌,
Jack opened his eyes,
杰克睁开眼睛,
[MUSIC]
(音乐)
You can take the long way home,
你可以把漫长的回家的路上,
[MUSIC]
(音乐)
Or edit a film,
或编辑一个电影,
[MUSIC]
(音乐)
Like this one,
喜欢这个,
[MUSIC],
(音乐)
When technology is designed for everyone,
当技术是为每个人设计的,
[MUSIC]
(音乐)
It lets anyone do what they love, including me,
它允许任何人做他们爱,包括我,
[MUSIC]
(音乐)
So the woman narrating and
所以女人叙述
whom you saw featured throughout that video is named
你看见谁在视频被命名为特色
Sady, and she has cerebral palsy,
回来,和她有脑瘫,
And she's the principal editor on that video,
她的主编,视频,
which I think is a powerful example of the way in which
我认为这是一个功能强大的方法的例子吗
technology can empower people with disabilities and
技术可以使残疾人
fundamentally change their lives,
从根本上改变他们的生活,
So that is really what accessibility is all about,
这是真正的可访问性,
It's making technology work for everyone,
是做技术工作的每个人,
making it accessible for everyone,
这使得每一个人,可
So let's take a look at some statistics,
让我们看看一些统计数据,
There are 285 million people worldwide who have some sort
全世界有2.85亿人一些
of low vision condition or who are entirely blind,
低视力的条件或完全失明,
There are 360 million who are hard of hearing or deaf,
有3.6亿个重听或失聪,
One in every 12 men is colorblind in some way, and 1
每12人是色盲,和1
in 68 children fall somewhere on the autism spectrum,
68年,儿童自闭症介于
And so what this means is that worldwide there are over
所以这意味着,全球有超过
a billion people that have a disability of some sort,
某种形式的残疾十亿人,
Or in other words, one in seven,
换句话说,七分之一,
So by no means is accessibility a small issue,
所以绝不可访问性是一个小问题,
It affects a lot of people and
它影响了很多人
if your app has an audience of any significant size you're
如果您的应用程序有任何重要的大小你的观众
going to have users that have disabilities,
有障碍的用户,
And you should be doing the best, your best to make sure
你应该做的最好的,最好的,以确保
that whatever you're working on works for everybody,
无论你在工作,
So at Apple we think of accessibility in four distinct
所以在苹果在四个不同的可访问性
groups,
组,
which includes things like autism, dyslexia, and
其中包括诸如自闭症、诵读困难和
other forms of learning disability,
其他形式的学习障碍,
Physical and motor skills, so people that have tremors or
身体和运动技能,所以人们有震动或
Parkinson's and maybe can't make precise movements
帕金森症,也许不能做出精确的运动
or gestures, but this also includes people who
或手势,但这也包括人
are paralyzed or have a limited set of digits that
瘫痪或一组有限的数字吗
they can use to interact with the system,
他们可以使用与系统交互,
For instance a single finger or a single toe, or
例如一个手指或一个脚趾,或
in Sadie's case, her head,
在赛迪的案例中,她的头,
Vision, which covers a spectrum of vision impairment
涵盖了一系列的愿景,障碍
from low vision to completely blind, and
从低视力完全失明
also includes different forms of color blindness,
还包括不同形式的色盲,
And finally we have hearing,
最后我们有听力,
which also like vision exists on a spectrum from the hard of
也喜欢视觉存在频谱的困难
hearing to the completely deaf,
听力完全失聪,
So now our team has developed a huge set of features on iOS
现在我们的团队开发了一个巨大的iOS的特征
that assists in all of these categories, and best of all
协助所有这些类别,最重要的是
they all come baked into the system from the beginning,
他们都来烤到系统从一开始,
So they're all on all of your iOS devices that you can turn
所以他们都是你的iOS设备上,你可以转弯
on, no add-ons required,
不需要插件,
And as much as I'd like to go feature by feature and
尽管我想去特性和功能
tell you why each of these is cool, and why it's necessary
告诉你为什么这些很酷,为什么它是必要的
and solves the problem, we don't have all night, so
和解决问题,我们没有一整夜,所以
I'm going to focus on just a couple,
我要关注几,
But I do encourage you to go and check them out for
但我鼓励你去检查他们
You can find accessibility settings on your device by
你可以找到可访问性设置你的设备
yourself,
你自己,
going to General and
一般,
tapping on Accessibility where you'll find a long list of
开发可访问性,你会发现一长串
all the features that you can enable on your devices,
的所有功能,您可以使在你的设备上,
What I'd like to do now though is demo for you,
我现在想做的是为你演示,
one of our most popular pieces of assistive technology which
我们最受欢迎的作品之一的辅助技术
is called VoiceOver,
被称为画外音,
It's a screen reader that allows blind and low vision
这是一个屏幕阅读器,允许盲和低视力
users to use a touch screen by audibly describing elements of
用户使用一个触摸屏,可听见地描述的元素
the screen as they pan or swipe around it,
屏幕上锅或刷卡时,
So without a technology like this, blind users would be
没有这样的技术,用户会视而不见
unable to use the iPhone which is why it's really important
无法使用iPhone,这就是为什么它是非常重要的
for you to take advantage of the API which I'm gonna get
你利用我要得到的API
into in a little bit so that your apps play well with it,
到一点,这样你的应用打好了,
So, I have my device here on the home screen and
所以,我在主屏幕和设备
I'm gonna turn VoiceOver on,
我要打开配音,
And what you're gonna notice is that it's going to focus on
你要注意的是,它会关注的
the first element of the screen,
第一个元素在屏幕的,
which is the Mail app in the upper left corner,
这是邮件应用程序在左上角,
VoiceOver on,
画外音,
Mail,
邮件,
No unread emails,
没有未读邮件,
And it described it to me, and told me some extra information
描述我,告诉我一些额外的信息
about it, for instance, that I have no unread emails,
,例如,我没有未读邮件,
So if I wanted to navigate between items,
如果我想导航条目之间,
if I wanna go item by item, I can swipe right or left,
如果我想去逐项,我可以左右滑动,
Calendar, photos, camera,
日历,照片,相机,
And it's going to read to me the description of each
和我要读的描述
But if we're on the home screen which I'm here fairly
但如果我们在主屏幕上,我是相当的
item as I go,
项目,我去,
frequently, I know my way around, I can also just feel
经常,我知道我的方式,我也可以感觉
my way around the screen with my finger,
我与我的手指在屏幕上,
You tapped on Music,
你在音乐了,
And once I found exactly what I'm looking for,
一旦我找到我在寻找什么,
a double tap acts like a single tap would when you
双击就像一个水龙头当你
don't have VoiceOver on,
没有解说,
So it's gonna open Music,
所以它会打开音乐,
Music, this is now playing screen, button,
音乐,现在玩屏幕,按钮,
Now because music is a first party application,
因为音乐是第一方的应用程序,
Apple engineers have gone through and
苹果公司的工程师已经通过
made sure that all of the UI in that app is accessible,
确保所有UI应用程序访问,
So VoiceOver interacts with this interface
所以画外音与这个接口
exactly the same way that it would on the home screen,
完全相同的方式,它将在主屏幕上,
I could swipe, [SOUND] Or
我可以刷卡,[声音]或
find exactly what I'm looking for,
发现我在找什么,
Now VoiceOver, because it is intercepting gestures
现在画外音,因为它是拦截动作
that are normally used for
这通常用于
other things when VoiceOver's turned off,
其他的事情当画外音的关闭,
There are analogs for
有类似物
each different kind of interaction with the system
每个不同的交互系统
that you might need when VoiceOver is turned on,
时,您可能需要配音,
So, for instance, with the track scrubber, if I only want
例如,追踪洗涤器,如果我只希望
to scrub through the track, if I don't have voice over on,
通过跟踪擦洗,如果我没有语音,
then I'm just gonna run my finger along it,
然后我要运行我的手指沿着它,
like a slider,
像一个滑块,
But when VoiceOver's on it's trying to
但当画外音的尝试
interpret that gesture as me trying to find an element,
解释这种姿态和我试图找到一个元素,
So instead we have this adjustable gesture on
所以我们有这个可调的姿态
items that are adjustable, I can swipe my finger up and
可调的物品,我可以刷我的手指
down to change the value,
变化的值,
8 seconds and 3 minutes,
8秒和3分钟,
30 seconds,
30秒,
So those are just some very,
这些只是一些非常,
very basic examples of how VoiceOver works,
非常基本的例子,画外音是如何工作的,
It's much more advanced than that when you get into
这是比,当你进入更高级的
the nitty, nitty gritty of it,
细节,细节,
And I highly encourage you to turn it on and
我强烈建议你打开它
play around with it and see what the experience is really
与它玩耍,看看经验是什么
like for a user who's blind,
像用户的盲人,
So where does the information that an assistive technology
那么,一个辅助技术的信息
like VoiceOver uses coming from?
像画外音使用来自?
Well it runs in it's own process on the system, and
它运行在它自己的系统上的过程,和
it uses the UIAccessibility protocol to communicate with
它使用UIAccessibility协议与通信
other processes, and
其他进程,
ask them information about the current element on the screen,
问他们关于当前元素在屏幕上的信息,
So VoiceOver will receive an input, for
所以画外音将获得一个输入
instance a single tap, and
实例一个水龙头,和
it will get the currently focused element's description,
它将当前集中元素的描述,
It will query the current process for predefined pieces
将查询当前进程预定义的碎片
of information about that element,
元素的信息,
And from those queries, it's going to stitch together
从这些查询,它会缝在一起
a user friendly description and speak it,
一个用户友好的描述和它说话,
So let's take a look at the different properties in
让我们看看不同的属性
the protocol that an assistive technology is going to
一个辅助技术将的协议
ask about,
询问,
The first, and arguably most important,
第一,可以说是最重要的,
is isAccessibilityElement which tells VoiceOver whether
是isAccessibilityElement告诉画外音
or not the current thing should even be visible to it,
甚至不是当前的事情应该是可见的,
And if this is set to no then obviously it's not going to be
如果这是设置为不那么显然不是
an accessible element and
一个访问元素和
VoiceOver will not be able to focus on it,
画外音将无法关注它,
But in the case of say, a volume slider,
但在说,音量滑块,
which I'm going to use as an example for
我将使用作为一个例子
all these properties, we're gonna set this value to true,
所有这些特性,我们将这个值设置为true,
Next we have the accessibilityLabel
接下来我们有accessibilityLabel
which describes what an element,
它描述了一个元素,
So in the case of the Volume slider, it changes the volume,
所以在音量滑块的情况下,改变体积,
so it's going to say Volume,
所以它会说体积,
And then you may wonder
然后你可能想知道
why we don't say something like Volume Slider,
为什么我们不这样说音量滑块,
And this is because of this next
这是因为下一个
property accessibilityTraits
财产accessibilityTraits
which is used to define what category an element fits into,
用于定义类别元素融入,
So in the case of a slider, it's an adjustable element,
所以在一个滑动条的情况下,这是一个可调的元素,
so we're going to give it the adjustable trait,
所以我们要给它可调特性,
This means that when VoiceOver describes it,
这意味着当画外音描述它,
it's going to say volume adjustable,
它会说体积可调,
which means that the word slider is redundant,
这意味着“滑块”这个词是多余的,
And doesn't need to be there,
不需要,
Accessibility traits
易访问性特征
are important in other ways as well,
在其他方面也很重要,
So certain traits afford elements certain behaviors,
因此某些特征元素特定的行为,
For instance, in my demo where I was showing the track
例如,在我的演示,我是跟踪显示
scrubber, that increment and decrement gesture is added
洗涤器,递增和递减的姿态
because that view has the adjustable trait set to it,
因为这一观点有可调节的特征集,
So, VoiceOver knows that that view is going to respond
画外音知道这一观点是要回应
in some way to having its value increased or decreased,
在某些方面有它的价值的增加或减少,
VoiceOver also has a mechanism for
画外音也的机制
navigating a display, where a user can say
导航显示,用户可以说
I want to navigate based on only this kind of item,
我只想导航基于这样的项目,
So, for instance, if I had a table view that I wanted to
例如,如果我有一个我想要的表视图
navigate just by its headers then I could set this in
导航的头然后我可以设置
VoiceOver, and it's going to go through and only focus on
画外音,它会通过,只关注
elements in the hierarchy that have the header trait,
头特征元素层次结构,
So it's important that all of your views have the right
所以重要的是你所有的有正确的看法
traits so they behave as expected to voice over users,
特征所以他们的行为符合预期时语音用户,
Next we have accessibility value,
接下来,我们有可访问性价值,
Which you can override if your view has some sort of state,
你可以覆盖如果你观点的某种状态,
So for example, the state for
例如,国家
the volume slider is what is the current percent
音量滑块是当前的百分比
that my volume is set to, and we're gonna return 50%,
我的音量设置为,我们会返还50%,
And finally, we have accessibilityHint,
最后,我们有accessibilityHint,
So this is another optional property that's meant
这是另一个可选属性的意思
to provide a more long-form description of what something
提供更多的长篇描述的东西
is or what something does,
或者什么东西,
This is important often for VoiceOver users who have never
这是重要的画外音用户从来没有经常
used your interface before and are trying to learn their way
使用接口之前,正在努力学习
around it and figure out how things work together,
,找出如何一起工作,
But you should never put information that is
但你永远不应该把信息
critical to the user in this description
用户在此描述的关键
because Accessibility can be turned off,
因为易访问性可以被关闭,
And therefore a user may not ever hear them,
因此用户可能没有听过他们,
Which they might do to keep VoiceOver from being
他们可能防止画外音
too verbose if they're an experienced user,
过于冗长,如果他们是一个有经验的用户,
So those are the fine five main accessibility traits,
这是优良的五个主要的易访问性特征,
Without them the interface is totally unusable to VoiceOver,
没有他们的接口是完全不可用画外音,
and that's the blind and low vision users who rely on it,
这是盲人和低视力用户依赖它,
UIKit views define these properties by default, or
UIKit视图定义这些属性在默认情况下,或
most of them do, which means that most of the legwork is
他们中的大多数,这意味着大多数的跑腿工作
already done for you,
已经完成了,
But what you really need to watch out for
但你真的需要小心
is your own custom views, so let's look at some code,
是您自己的自定义视图,所以让我们来看看代码,
Let's say that I have a view controller
假设我有一个视图控制器
that has a property image view of subclass MyImageView,
有一个属性图像视图MyImageView子类,
which is a subclass that I've created,
这是我创建的一个子类,
It's just a UIView, it's not a UIImageView or
它只是一个UIView,这不是UIImageView或
anything like that, so
类似的,所以
it doesn't have accessibility by default,
它没有可访问性在默认情况下,
Well in my viewDidLoad method I'm obviously gonna call
在我viewDidLoad方法显然会调用
super and then I could do this,
超级然后我可以这样做,
I could use dot notation to set each of these different
我可以使用点符号设置这些不同
properties,
属性,
I'm gonna say yes my
我要说是我的
imageView,isAccessibilityElem- ent,
imageView isAccessibilityElem - ent,
I'm gonna give it some reasonable label and I'm gonna
我要给它一些合理的标签,我要
give it the trait, the image trait, because I want it to
给它的特征,图像特征,因为我想要的
behave like any other image would on the system,
像任何其他图片会在系统上,
Now, I probably want to do this in a case where these
现在,我可能需要做这些
values depend on an instance of a view,
值取决于一个视图的一个实例,
But, there may be a case where
但是,可能存在一种情况
the value that is returned from one of these properties
返回的值从这些属性之一
applies to all view of that kind,
适用于所有的那种,
So, on the subclass MyImageView,
所以,MyImageView子类,
I could have instead overridden the getter for
我可以而不是覆盖的getter
isAccessibilityElement always return true,
isAccessibilityElement始终返回true,
If I know that MyImageView is never not
如果我知道MyImageView从来都不是
going to be an accessibility
将是一个可访问性
element than this is probably what I want to do,
元素比这可能是我想做的,
Or if there's some internal logic to that class that
或者如果有一些类的内部逻辑
determines whether or not I should determine true or
决定我是否应该确定真正的或
false from here, this is a much better way to do that,
假的,这是一个更好的办法,
And then I can override the setter to just do nothing
然后我可以覆盖setter什么也不做
this applies to all of the properties,
这适用于所有的属性,
I can override them, their getters and
我可以覆盖它们,它们的getter和
setters explicitly,
setter明确,
So, now I'd like to demo what you've just seen
所以,现在我想演示你刚才看到什么
on a sample app that I've been working on,
在一个示例应用程序,我一直在工作,
So I'm gonna go back over here to my device and
所以我要回去我的设备和
I'm gonna turn VoiceOver back on,
我要打开画外音回来,
VoiceOver on,
画外音,
So you see down here I have this app called Notecards,
所以你看下面我有这个程序称为卡片,
[INAUDIBLE] Note note cards,
卡(INAUDIBLE)注意,注意,
It's just a basic app that has stacks of notecards that I
这只是一个基本的应用程序栈的卡片
can use to test myself,
可以使用它来测试自己,
And I need to do an accessibility audit of this
我需要做一个可访问性审计
app to see how well it works with VoiceOver,
应用程序,看看它如何使用画外音,
So, I'm gonna start by tapping on the first thing I see,
所以,我要开始利用我看到的第一件事,
which is that collection header,
那就是收集头,
Collection,
收藏
So, as you saw it read the label collection but
所以,当你看到它读标签但集合
what it didn't say was header,
它没有说什么头,
So I have no idea that this thing
所以我不知道这个东西
is actually a label that is meant to be a header for
实际上是一个标签,是一个头
all of the content underneath it,
下面所有的内容,
So that's the first thing I need to do is add that trait,
这就是我需要做的第一件事就是添加特征,
Add button,
添加按钮,
That button has a sensible label,
按钮有一个合理的标签,
Physics five cards,
物理五张牌,
That seems right,
这似乎是正确的,
Image one button,
图片一个按钮,
That doesn't seem right,
这似乎不正确的,
Image two button,
图像两个按钮,
And neither does that so both of these buttons
和也没有,所以这两个按钮
are missing accessibility labels and so
缺少可访问性标签和
I have actually no idea what they do,
我已经不知道他们做什么,
And it said image one and two because VoiceOver
它说图片1和2因为画外音
by default when it doesn't have a label on something that
默认情况下,当它没有标签的东西
uses an image like a UIButton, it's going to default to that
使用一个图像像UIButton,它会默认
image's filename as a last resort to try and see if it
图片的文件名作为最后的手段,试图看看它
can get something meaningful out of what this element is,
可以得到有意义的这个元素是什么,
So I need to instead add my own labels to those buttons,
所以我需要添加自己的标签的按钮,
Trivia, nine trivia,
琐事,九琐事,
Now if I go in here,
现在,如果我在这里,
I heard that that had the header trait,
我听说有头特征,
Add button,
添加按钮,
That has a good label,
一个好的标签,
Close button,
关闭按钮,
And if I come in here,
如果我来这里,
The phrase "Let them eat cake" is commonly
“让他们吃蛋糕”是常见的
attributed to whom?
归功于谁?
Queen Marie Antoinette,
I notice that these two labels,
我注意到这两个标签,
even though VoiceOver's picking them up,
尽管画外音的捡起来,
they are picked up as separate elements and so, I don't
他们拿起作为单独的元素,所以,我不喜欢
really have any context for how they work together,
真的没有任何上下文他们如何一起工作,
One is the question and one is the answer,
一个问题,一个是答案,
And it would actually be much better and give VoiceOver
它会更好,给画外音
users much context if I were to group them together,
用户上下文如果我组在一起,
That's one element and
这是一个元素和
say this is the question, this is the answer,
说这是一个问题,这是答案,
So they can actually understand what's happening in
所以他们可以理解发生了什么
this interface,
这个接口,
So I'm gonna go over to some code, to my app,
所以我要去一些代码,我的应用程序,
The first thing I wanna take care of is that header trade
首先我想照顾这个头贸易
cuz it's pretty easy,
因为它很简单,
And I have this title label right here, so
和我这里的标题标签,所以
I'm going to say accessibility traits or equals header,
我要说的可访问性特征或等于头,
Now I'm using or equals instead of just explicitly
现在我使用或=而不是显式地
equals, because I don't know what the superclass of title
=,因为我不知道标题的超类
label, what traits it is added to
标签,它被添加到什么特征
this accessibility element that it wants to have there,
可访问性元素,它想要,
So I don't wanna override whatever it set,
所以我不想覆盖任何设置,
I just wanna add my own in,
我想增加我自己的,
So that's what I'm doing there,
这是我在做什么,
Next, let's look at this cell and the shuffle, and
接下来,让我们看看这个细胞和洗牌,和
delete button,
删除按钮,
So I need to add accessibility labels for
所以我需要添加可访问性标签
these and come here and say
这些和来这里说
shuffleButton,accessibilityLa- bel,
shuffleButton accessibilityLa -贝尔,
Shuffle seems like a reasonable label to give it,
洗牌似乎是一个合理的标签给它,
I'm gonna say delete button equals delete,
等于删除,点击删除按钮
This seems to convey to me what exactly these buttons
这似乎传达我究竟这些按钮
are supposed to do,
是应该做的,
And finally, I'm gonna come to this collection view cell
最后,我要来到这个集合视图细胞
to have this question and answer,
这个问题和答案,
What I'm gonna do here
我要做什么
is override these methods or these properties,
是覆盖这些方法或属性,
So I'm gonna override this accessibility element to
所以我要覆盖此可访问性元素
always return true on the cell itself so
始终返回true细胞本身
that the entire cell has the accessibility element
整个单元的可访问性元素
instead of each individual label,
而不是每个标签,
I'm gonna set the label to return Question,
我要设置标签返回的问题,
then the question's text,
问题的文本,
Answer, and then the answer's text,
回答,然后答案的文本,
And I'm going to add the button trait to it because
我要添加按钮特质,因为
that cell is a button where I can go in and edit the card,
细胞是一个按钮,我可以编辑卡,
And I need to convey that to the user,
我需要传达给用户,
So let's build this,
所以让我们构建这个,
Notecards,
卡片,
[SOUND] Notecards, collections heading,
[声音]卡片,集合,
So I've got the header trait,
我有头特征,
Tab physics shuffle button delete button,
选项卡物理洗牌按钮删除按钮,
Both buttons have the right labels,
两个按钮有正确的标签,
Trivia, link trivia, trivia question: the phrase "Let them
琐事、链接琐事花絮的问题:“让他们
eat cake" is commonly attributed to whom?
吃蛋糕”通常被归功于谁?
Answer Queen Marie Antoinette,
回答玛丽·安托瓦内特王后,
So, I've got it behaving exactly as I want it,
我有它的行为就像我想要的,
just a few simple lines of code,
几行简单的代码,
That's just a couple examples of some of the issues that you
这只是几个例子,你的一些问题
might find in your own apps,
可能会发现在您自己的应用程序,
So I'm gonna go back, to my account,
所以我要回去,我的账户,
I also would like to touch on- VoiceOver off,
我也想触摸——画外音,
The idea of containers,
容器的想法,
So aside from the attributes,
所以除了属性,
We also have the accessibility container protocol,
我们也有可访问性容器协议,
So let's say that I am the engineer who has been
假设我是工程师
tasked with coding this view in the Calendar app,
负责编码这一观点的日历应用程序,
it's the year view,
今年看来,
And I've decided that I am going to design this view so
我已经决定我要设计这一观点
that each week is its own custom UIView,
每周都是自己的自定义UIView,
And within that UIView's drawRect method,
和在UIView绘制矩形的方法中,
I'm going to explicitly draw all the days of the week,
我要明确画出所有的日子,
Now because those views that I've drawn aren't standard
现在因为这些观点,我画的不是标准
UIKit views,
UIKit视图,
they don't inherit accessibility by default,
他们不继承访问默认情况下,
And I don't really have an easy way of setting
我没有一个简单的方法设置
the accessibility properties on each of them,
每个人都可访问性属性,
But what we'd like for
但是我们想要的
them to be is visible to VoiceOver one day at a time,
他们是可见的画外音一天一次,
And so that I can navigate them day by day and
所以,我可以每天和导航
get a description for each day at a time,
每天一次,得到一个描述
rather than each week at a time,
而不是一次每周,
So I need to do is create a set of accessibility elements
所以我需要做的是创建一组可访问性元素
from scratch that overlay these day views and
从头视图和覆盖这些天
return them as sub-elements of my accessibility, or
返回我的易访问性作为子元素,或
of my week view container,
我的星期视图容器,
So what does that look like in code?
代码中看起来像什么?
Well, I have this MyWeekView class,
好吧,我有这个MyWeekView类,
Which I'm going to explicitly say is not an accessibility
我要明确地说不是一个可访问性
element, because I instead want VoiceOver to go through
元素,而是因为我想让画外音
and find the sub-elements of it that are accessible,
访问并找到它的子元素,
And I'm going to create an array of elements that
我要创建一个数组的元素
are UIAccessibilityElement,
UIAccessibilityElement,
I'm going to iterate over the days of the week that
我要遍历的一周的日子
are in that week,
在那一周,
And for each one I'm going to create an accessibility
为每一个和我要创建一个可访问性
element, with the accessibility container set
与可访问性容器元素,集
as myself, because I'm the one that contains it,
作为我自己,因为我是一个包含它,
I'm going to set its label to be something
我要设置它的标签
sensible for that day,
明智的那一天,
And now I'm going to set this property
现在我要设置该属性
accessibilityFrameInContainer- Space,
accessibilityFrameInContainer——空间,
Now, this is crucial because it indicates to VoiceOver
现在,这是至关重要的,因为它表明画外音
where the element is on the screen, so that when I'm
在屏幕上的元素,所以当我吗
panning around with my finger VoiceOver knows where it is,
平移在我的手指画外音知道它在哪里,
So if my finger is over it, it can describe it to me and
如果我的手指,它可以描述它对我
see that I'm trying to focus on that element,
看到我想关注的元素,
It's also what VoiceOver uses to draw the bounding box,
这也是什么画外音用来绘制边界框,
And in case you couldn't tell this frame should be in
如果你不能告诉这个框架应该在
the coordinate space of its container,
坐标空间的容器,
So once I do that, I'll pan the element to my array of
一旦我这样做,我将锅里的元素的数组
accessibility elements, and then, I will set the property
可访问性的元素,然后,我将设置的属性
on MyWeekView accessibility elements to be those elements,
这些元素MyWeekView可访问性元素,
And what this says is these are all my accessible
这说的是这些都是我的访问
sub-elements and VoiceOver should navigate them
子元素和画外音应该浏览它们
in the order that I returned them in this array,
我返回这个数组的顺序,
So, let's take a look at adding that to my sample app,
所以,让我们看一看,我的样本应用程序,
Let me go back over here,
让我回到这里,
And turn the VoiceOver back on,
打开配音,
VoiceOver on now,
画外音在现在,
So you may have wondered
所以你可能不知道
what this shuffle button actually does,
实际上这个洗牌按钮,
Well, it shuffles the cards in the deck and puts them up so
它打乱卡片在甲板上,使它们
I can test them,
我可以测试他们,
Shuffle trivia heading,
洗牌小标题,
And what I have down here,
我在这里,
this little circle view is just a little UI to
这个小圆的观点只是一个小的UI
indicate to me how far I am through the deck,
告诉我多少我穿过甲板,
So if I go to the next card for instance- Next question,
例如如果我进入下一个卡片,下一个问题,
It's increasing because I'm filling out the circle
增加因为我填写这个圆
with how many cards I've done,
我做了有多少卡,
However if I stay to swipe to it,
但是如果我留下来刷,
Next question, from next question,
下一个问题,从下一个问题,
I hear a bonk and
我听到一个性交
try to run my finger I'm also hearing a bonk,
尝试运行我的手指,我还听到一个性交,
So what that indicates is that when I swiped and
这表明当我刷卡
did it it means there's nothing left on the screen for
它意味着没有什么离开在屏幕上吗
VoiceOver to swipe to you've hit the last element,
画外音来刷你打最后一个元素,
And when I'm running my finger over it means that there's
当我运行它意味着有我的手指
nothing below my finger that is an accessible element,
不低于我的手指是一个访问元素,
But we'd really like that to be accessible to VoiceOver
但我们真的想画外音都可以访问
users, so they can track their progress through this stack,
用户,这样他们就可以通过这个堆栈跟踪他们的进展,
And so we're gonna use
所以我们要使用
accessibility elements to accomplish this,
可访问性元素来实现这个目标,
So I'm gonna come back over to my code,
所以我要回来到我的代码,
I'm gonna go to this ShuffleStatusView,
我要去这个ShuffleStatusView,
which is where I've done the drawing of this circle,
这是我做的画圆,
I'm gonna copy and paste,
我要复制粘贴,
So, what I've done here is I've created
所以,我在这里所做的是我创建的
an AccessibilityElement with myself as the container,
一个AccessibilityElement以自己为容器,
I set its label to be card, whatever the current card
我设置它的标签卡,无论当前卡
number is, of the total amount of cards,
号码是,总额的卡片,
I've set its accessibilityFrame
我设置其accessibilityFrame
to be the frame of the circle,
圆的框架,
And in my AccessibilityElements because
在我AccessibilityElements因为
the previous and
前面的,
next button are also part of the StatusView,
next按钮也StatusView的一部分,
I don't want them to be left out from VoiceOver,
我不想让他们从画外音被排除在外,
So I'm gonna also include those in my
所以我要还包括那些在我
AccessibilityElements along with the new element that
AccessibilityElements随着新元素
I've just created,
我刚刚创建的,
So let's see if that worked,
让我们看看如果工作,
NoteCards, NoteCards, collect,
收集卡片,卡片,
shuffle button, shuffle, trivia, previous question,
调整按钮,洗牌,琐事,先前的问题,
I've got my previous button,
我有我以前的按钮,
Next question, problem, part one of nine,
下一个问题,问题,部分的九个,
So now it's become accessible,
现在可以访问,
And pretty easy, not too many lines of code,
很简单,没有太多行代码,
We can go back,
我们可以回去,
So I'd like to change gears for a minute, and
所以我想改变齿轮一会儿,和
talk a little bit about some visual accommodations that you
谈谈一些你的视觉住宿
should be aware of when you're designing your app,
应该意识到当你设计你的应用时,
So the first thing is color,
首先是颜色,
Color is a useful means of differentiating information,
颜色是一种有用的微分信息,
but if it's the sole differentiator
但如果这是唯一的区别
then users who are colorblind won't be able to fully
然后用户色盲无法完全
understand the user interface,
理解用户界面,
So, take for example this view in Mail,
所以,例如这一观点在邮件,
Our designers wanted the unread and
我们的设计师想要读
flagged messages to be differentiated apart from each
分化标记消息除了
other with circle views that are of a particular color,
其他与圆视图的一个特定的颜色,
But to a colorblind user, they can't tell the difference,
但一个色盲的用户,他们不能区分,
So what we did, is we added a setting in Mail so that you
我们所做的,我们添加了一个邮件,以便您的设置
can change flag messages to use shape and color,
可以改变国旗消息使用形状和颜色,
And what this does is it uses both color and shape to convey
这是它使用两个颜色和形状来传达
meaning so that no user has to be left out,
意思,没有用户必须离开,
So, if you're writing an app that uses color to
因此,如果您正在编写一个应用程序,它使用颜色
convey meaning,
传达的意思,
then you should consider doing something similar,
然后你应该考虑做类似的事情,
Now color can also be too bright, distracting, and
现在的颜色也可以太亮,分散注意力
contrast and transparency and
对比和透明度和
blurring can all have negative impacts on legibility for
模糊可以在易读性都有负面影响
people that have certain vision conditions,
人有一定的视觉条件下,
This is the default control center on iOS and
这是默认在iOS和控制中心
as you can see color bleeds through from behind and
正如你所看到的颜色通过从后面和出血
is blurred by the control center's background,
由控制中心的背景模糊,
But if I turn on the darken colors and
但是如果我打开加深颜色
reduce transparency setting,
降低透明度设置,
we no longer get those colors bleeding through from behind,
我们不再把那些颜色流血通过从后面,
And the contrast between the colors and
和颜色之间的对比
the lighter background is much more stark,
较轻的背景更加鲜明,
which means that it's a lot more readable to those users
这意味着用户更多的可读吗
that have those vision conditions,
这些视觉条件,
So you can check whether things like these are enabled
所以你可以检查是否启用了这样的事情
through these two UIKit functions,
通过这两个UIKit功能,
And this way, you can adapt your interface to the needs
和这种方式,您可以调整您的接口需求
of your users rather than having to try and create
用户而不是尝试和创造
some design that, from the get go, applies to everybody,
一些设计的,适用于每个人,
Now for this next one, I'm going to say that anybody in
现在下一个,我说任何人
the room who gets motion sick from phone animation should
房间里谁从手机动画应该运动病
probably look away for a second,
可能去寻找第二个,
Device is gonna show these standard
设备会显示这些标准
app opening animation,
应用程序打开动画,
So you can see that when I tap on music,
所以你可以看到,当我点击音乐,
the app expands from its place on the dock, and
应用扩展其在码头,和
the screen swoops in to center on it,
屏幕上俯冲而下,中心,
But if I turn on the reduce motion setting,
但是如果我打开设置,减少运动
I instead get this cross fade,
我得到这个交叉混合,而是
So there are certain people with vestibular disorders
所以有一定的前庭障碍患者
that can be triggered by complex motion which most
可以由最复杂的运动
often results in things like nausea and dizziness,
往往导致恶心和头晕,
So you should be mindful of any animations in your app,
所以你应该注意你的应用程序的任何动画,
particularly if they cause a lot of movement or
特别是如果他们造成很多运动或
are unexpected in some way,
在某种程度上意想不到的,
You should consider enabling an alternative
你应该考虑启用另一种选择
animation when this setting is enabled which you can check
动画启用该设置时,你可以检查
through a similar UIKit function,
通过一个类似UIKit函数,
Now the final visual accommodation that I'd like
我想现在最后视觉调节
to talk about today relates to typography, and
谈论今天与排版
it's dynamic type which is a feature in iOS that allows
这是动态类型iOS中一个功能,允许
a user to scale their font,
用户规模的字体,
And I believe you touched on it very briefly,
我相信你感动很短暂,
There are many users out there who struggle to use devices
有许多用户很难使用设备
because the type is so small, or so thin that it ends up
因为类型是如此之小,薄,最终
blurring together, and they can't read it,
模糊起来,他们不能读它,
And this applies to people with low vision conditions,
这适用于低视力患者的条件,
but it also applies to people whose vision is simply
但它也适用于人的愿景是简单
deteriorated from age, or
从年龄、恶化或
people who simply need to wear glasses,
人只需要戴眼镜,
So, Dynamic Type is meant to help adapt these
因此,动态类型是为了帮助适应这些
people's devices to their needs,
人们对他们的需求的设备,
Now on the left you see the standard Mail inbox interface
现在左边你会看到标准的邮件收件箱界面
with the default text,
使用默认文本,
And on the right I've scaled it up several levels,
我右边的按比例缩小的多个层面,
And as you can see,
正如你所看到的,
the interface has adapted itself and the layout as well
接口已经适应了本身和布局
to accommodate the larger text size,
以适应更大的文本大小,
The most common way that you're gonna get this behavior
最常见的方式,你会得到这种行为
is by using this method preferredFont(forTextStyle,
通过使用这种方法preferredFont(forTextStyle,
which is a class method on UIFont,
这是一个类方法UIFont,
When you set the font of a UILabel or
当你设置字体UILabel或
UITextView, using this method, the font will be scaled to
UITextView,使用这种方法,字体将被推广
the user's preference using the system font,
用户的偏好使用系统字体,
And what you do is you pass through a TextStyle, which
和你要做的就是通过TextStyle,
indicates what the general purpose of the text is,
显示文本的一般目的是什么,
So titles are large and body is a more standard size,
所以标题是大型和身体是一个标准尺寸,
There are these eight distinct styles that you can pass this
有这八截然不同的风格,你可以通过这个
method and each of them have pre-defined point sizes and
方法和每个人都有预定义的点大小和
weight sizes to them,
尺寸,重量
So, let's look at some code where I used that,
所以,让我们来看看一些代码,我使用,
So let's say I have MyLabelView which is
假设我有MyLabelView就是
a custom UIView, and it has a sub label or
自定义UIView,子标签或
a sub view that is of class UILabel,
子视图的UILabel类,
Now in my init method, I'm going to init that label,
现在我在init方法,我要初始化标签,
Now, I'm gonna set its number of lines to be 0,
现在,我要设置它的行数为0,
And what this indicates to the UILabel, is that it doesn't
这表明UILabel,是它不
need to be limited to any specific number of lines,
需要限制在任何特定的行数,
It can actually grow to an unbounded number of lines,
它可以长到一个无界的行数,
Which is important when I'm growing the text size because
这是很重要的因为当我越来越多的文本尺寸的
as I get bigger and bigger, it's likelier, it's more and
当我越来越大,更有可能,它是越来越
more likely that I'm not gonna be able to fit whatever
更有可能的是,我无法适应
text I have on a single line,
文字在一行,
Now I also need to set adjustsFontForContentSizeCate-
现在我还需要设置adjustsFontForContentSizeCate -
gory to be true, and what this does is it tells the label
血淋淋的是真实的,这是它讲述了标签
that when the user has changed their font size and
当用户改变了他们的字体大小和
my app is opened in the background, I need to update,
我的程序在后台打开,我需要更新,
The label needs to update itself to match whatever
标签需要更新本身来匹配
the new font that I've changed my size to is,
新字体,于是我改变了大小,
And then I am going to use that preferredFont
然后我要用这个preferredFont
forTextStyle,
Probably just gonna use body,
可能只是用身体,
because it's standard in this case and then add my subview,
因为它是标准的在这种情况下,然后添加我的子视图,
Now, what do you do in the case where you wanna use
现在,你会怎么做如果你想使用
a custom point size when you're at the default
一个自定义点当你在默认大小
text size?
文本大小?
Or you even wanna use a custom font but
甚至你想使用一个自定义字体
you still wanna support dynamic type,
你仍然想支持动态类型,
I did this in my own sample app,
我在我自己的样例应用程序,
it uses the boldSystemFontOfSize method,
它使用boldSystemFontOfSize方法,
which is not going to automatically be scaled to
它不会自动缩放
the user's preference,
用户的偏好,
So, what I'm gonna do is I'm going to take advantage of
所以,我要做的就是我要利用
this property on UIApplication preferredContestSizeCategory,
这个属性在UIApplication preferredContestSizeCategory,
And what this tells me,
这告诉我,
is what the user has currently set their font to,
是目前用户设置的字体,
Now there are seven distinct size categories at default,
现在有七个不同的大小类别违约,
The large size is the default size on iOS,
大号的是iOS上默认大小,
But there are also five more accessibility sizes and
但也有五个可访问性大小和
located in accessibility settings that can make
位于易访问性设置
the text really, really big,
文本非常大,
So what would my code for something like this look like?
我的代码,这样看起来像什么?
Well, I'd probably create some sort of NSObject like
嗯,我可能会创建一些NSObject像
MyFontManager, that will be an object that will manage all
MyFontManager,那将是一个对象,将管理所有
the fonts for my app so that I can run everything through it,
字体为我的应用程序,这样我可以通过它运行一切,
And then I'd have some method like this,
然后我有一些方法,
where I'd use a fontSize variable and write a switch
我使用一个字形大小变量和写一个开关呢
statement that changes the value of the fontSize based
声明,基于改变字形大小的值
on what my sizeCategory is set to, to some sensible value,
什么我的sizeCategory将一些合理的值,
I mean to do that for every case,
我的意思是,每一个案例中,
And then I'm gonna use whatever the method
然后我将使用的方法
I was going to use before, like systemFont(ofSize: or
我要使用之前,像systemFont(ofSize:或
my custom font or boldSystemFont(ofSize:
我的自定义字体或boldSystemFont(ofSize:
using whatever size I determined was appropriate for
我决定使用任何大小是合适的
the current size class,
当前大小类,
Now it's also important that I register myself to listen for
现在也很重要,我自己注册监听
the UIContentSizeCategoryDidChange
的UIContentSizeCategoryDidChange
notification,
通知,
Because I'm no longer using that preferred font for
因为我不再使用首选的字体
text style method so all my views aren't gonna know that
文本样式的方法所以我的观点不会知道
they need to update themselves when the font size changes,
他们需要更新自己当字体大小变化时,
So I'm gonna register myself as an observer on this
所以我要自己注册一个观察者
notification and just write a method that updates
通知和写一个更新的方法
my fonts in some sort of sensible way,
我的字体以某种合理的方式,
So let's move for the final time to my demo app,
让我们最后一次我的演示应用程序,
and see what it's like with dynamic type,
用动态类型,看看是什么样子的
Now for this, I'm actually gonna exit full screen,
现在,我真的要退出全屏,
And I'm going to bring up this tool in Xcode called
我要把这个工具在Xcode中调用
the Accessibility Inspector,
可访问性检查,
Now this is a super useful tool that I don't really have
这是一个非常有用的工具,我真的没有
time to go in to today about how you can use it,
时间去今天如何使用它,
But, it's an app that's built into Xcode that allows you to
但是,这是一个建在Xcode,允许您的应用程序
audit your own application for
审计自己的申请
all of its accessibility problems,
所有的可访问性问题,
And there's a great video from last year's WWDC that you can
有一个伟大的视频从去年的WWDC可以
find on the developer website to go through exactly
开发者网站上发现的经过
how you used this app,
你如何使用这个应用程序,
which I will have a link to at the end of the presentation,
我将有一个链接到结束的时候,
But for now, I'm going to attach to my phone and
但是现在,我要把我的电话
simply use it to change the font size dynamically so
简单地使用它动态地更改字体大小
that you can see what happens on the screen, what I do,
在屏幕上你可以看到发生了什么,我做什么,
So I'm gonna come to my stack of cards, and
所以我要来参加我的卡片,和
I can see that the number of
我可以看到很多
lines is already set to zero because this label is growing
行已经设置为0,因为这个标签正在增长
based on how much text I have there as I want it to,
基于文本多少我有我想要的,
But we're gonna see,
但我们要看到,
is as I change this value here with the slider,
是我改变这个值与滑块,
my text isn't updating at all, the content size,
我的文字不更新,内容的大小,
So something is wrong,
所以的东西是错误的,
So I'm gonna come over here to MyFontManager,
所以我要来这里MyFontManager,
And I'm gonna go look at my appFont method and
我要去看我的appFont方法和
I see the problem immediately,
我立刻发现问题,
I'm not adapting myself to what the preferred contentSize
我不适应自己首选contentSize
is and I'm not using the preferred font for
我不使用首选的字体吗
text style method,
文本样式的方法,
So I'm gonna replace that, With this,
所以我要更换,,
which takes this size and,
以这个尺寸,
based on some multiplier that I decided looks good,
基于一些乘数,我决定看起来不错,
I'm going to modify what the font size is,
我要修改字体大小是什么,
based on the SizeCategory,
基于SizeCategory,
And I'm going to return that using my
我要用我的回报
boldSystemFont(ofSize:,
Now, like I said,
现在,就像我说的,
I also need to register for that notification, so
我也需要注册通知,
that my view actually updates itself in real time,
实际上,我认为实时更新本身,
So we're gonna go to that cell,
所以我们要去那个细胞,
And I'm going to add myself as an observer,
我要添加自己作为一个观察者,
not to put that there,
不是把,,
And in my contentSizeCategoryChange
在我contentSizeCategoryChange
method, I'm just going to update the fonts here,
方法,我将更新这里的字体,
And that should work, hopefully, so let's rebuild,
这应该工作,希望让我们重建,
So I'm gonna come back over here,
所以我要回到这里,
I'm gonna open this and
我要打开这个
I'm gonna bring up my Accessibility Inspector again,
我要把我的可访问性检查,
And now as I change the size you see that it's growing
现在我改变你看到它不断增长的规模
bigger, and bigger, until it's real, real big,
大,大,直到它是真实的,真正的大,
And everything works exactly as I was expecting it to,
和一切工作和我预期的一样,
And, not a huge change,
不是一个巨大的变化,
So, I've covered several ways that you as a develop,
所以,我介绍几种方法,你开发,
developer can make your app more accessible to people,
开发人员可以使您的应用程序更容易,
This can actually be a great way to get your app featured
这可以成为一个伟大的方式让你的应用程序中
on the store,
在商店,
So we have sections that are devoted specifically to
我们有专门致力于部分
general purpose applications,
通用的应用程序,
That we think we've done
我们认为我们所做的一切
a good job with their accessibility,
一份好工作的可访问性,
For instance, this collection of apps that
例如,这个应用程序的集合
are good to use with VoiceOver,
使用画外音是好事,
Beyond making your own app accessible,
除了让你自己的应用程序可访问,
there's also a whole set of apps that are aimed at
还有一整套旨在应用
accessible users specifically,
具体来说,访问用户
So, I'd like to run through a few of those examples with
所以,我想通过几个的例子
you today,
你今天,
We have knfbReader, which is an app that scans
我们knfbReader,这是一个应用程序,扫描
text in real time, and let's users who are low vision or
实时文本,低视力或用户
blind interact with things like paper or
盲人与纸或交互
a restaurant menu, so they can read it,
餐厅菜单,所以他们可以阅读它,
We have an app like Ava, which transcribes conversations in
我们有一个应用程序像艾娃,转录的对话
real time, so that a user who's hard of hearing or
实时,这样用户的重听或
even deaf, can follow a conversation easier,
甚至失聪,可以按照交谈变得更容易,
And this includes a feature that actually breaks
这包括一个功能,实际上打破
conversation down, differentiating the different
谈话下来,区分不同的
speakers by color so I can tell who is speaking,
演讲者通过颜色我可以告诉是谁说,
And finally we have this app, Children with Autism,
最后我们有这个程序,自闭症儿童,
which is a visual scheduler built specifically for
这是一个视觉调度器专门为
children with autism,
自闭症儿童,
And allows them to be more independent and
并允许他们更独立
understand what they need to do,
了解他们需要做什么,
during their day as they are going along, task by task,
在天他们会,任务的任务,
So these are just a couple of examples,
这些只是几个例子,
And you may wonder, why am I telling you about this?
你可能想知道,为什么我要告诉你吗?
Well, basically, if you're looking for a possible idea
基本上,如果你正在寻找一个可能的想法
for a class of what you might want to work on,
针对一类你可能想工作,
Or the next great thing that you think you wanna work on,
或者下一个伟大的事情,你认为你想工作,
I encourage you to check out some of the work that's being
我鼓励您的工作的
done in accessibility because there are a lot of problems
在可访问性,因为有很多问题
that still aren't solved, and that are worthwhile to tackle,
仍然没有解决,这是有价值的解决,
Now, I've covered a lot today and
现在,我今天已经涵盖了许多
there's more that you can find on the web,
有更多的,你在网上可以找到,
These are a couple of links to some resources that you might
这些是几个你可能的一些资源的链接
find useful, including some of the things that I spoke about
找到有用的,包括一些我谈到的事情
during the presentation today,
在今天的演讲,
I would encourage you to check out some of these WWDC videos,
我鼓励你去看看这些WWDC的视频,
In particular,
特别是,
including the one on inclusive app design,
包括一个包含应用程序设计,
which is a whole session on design, focused on
整个会话在设计,关注吗
both accessibility as well as internationalization,
可访问性和国际化,
And that auditing your apps for accessibility,
审核你的应用程序的可访问性,
which goes through how to take advantage of the accessibility
通过如何利用的可访问性
inspector to make your own apps accessible,
检查员使您自己的应用程序可访问,
So, in closing,
所以,最后,
I'd like to circle back to the why of it all,
我想圆的原因,
Why should you take the time to do something like this?
你为什么要花时间去这样做吗?
Let me read you this quote from Sady, the woman who,
从回来,让我读你这句话的女人,
from the video that I showed at the beginning,
从一开始,我显示的视频
My love for technology is more than just a passion,
我对技术不仅仅是一个激情的爱,
It gives me access to my world,
它给了我进入我的世界,
I need help in some areas, but assistive technology
我需要帮助在某些地区,但辅助技术
enables me to communicate with my loved ones, and
让我与我的亲人沟通,
pursue my career,
追求我的事业,
What everybody else can do with a keyboard and
用键盘和其他人能做什么
a mouse, I can do with my two switches,
一只老鼠,我可以与我的两个开关,
The common person's life is enhanced by technology,
一般人的生活是增强技术,
But for somebody like Sady, technology is transformative,
但是有人喜欢回来,技术变革,
It can make them independent in ways that really couldn't
它可以让他们独立的方式,真的不能
have been imagined ten years ago,
一直想象的十年前,
It can allow them to do jobs that they couldn't have done,
它可以让他们做他们不能做的工作,
have hobbies that they couldn't have had, or
有他们不能有爱好,还是
experience the world in ways that they couldn't have,
体验世界的方式,他们不可能,
So by taking the time and putting in the effort to make
通过花时间和努力
sure that the work you do works for everyone, you can
确保你做的工作适合每一个人,你可以
have a lasting, meaningful impact on people's lives,
有一个持久的、有意义的影响人们的生活,
I promise you that you'll never find a more loyal
我向你保证,你将永远不会找到一个更加忠诚
customer than the one whose life you made better,
客户比你的生活更好,
Now I know that some of you may be thinking that that's
现在我知道,你们中的一些人可能会认为这是
great and all, but there are some things that
很棒,但有一些事情
really just don't work with accessibility,
真的只是不使用可访问性,
And I challenge you to think different,
我挑战你认为不同,
If you'd asked somebody 15 years ago how a blind person
如果你问某人15年前一个盲人如何
could use a touch screen,
可以使用一个触摸屏,
they probably would have told you that they couldn't,
他们可能会告诉你,他们不能,
And that's not true today,
今天,这不是真的,
Anything is really possible when you put your mind to it,
任何事情都是可能当你把你的思想,
So this is a video of my colleague Ryan DJing at last
这是一个视频,我的同事最后瑞恩打碟
year's WWDC,
WWDC,
Where we awarded the app djay Pro for
我们授予应用djay Pro在哪里
their work on accessibility,
他们的工作在可访问性,
He DJed live on stage using the app with VoiceOver and
他dj活在舞台上使用应用程序和画外音
I'd like to play this brief clip for you now,
我想玩这个简短的视频给你现在,
I have an iPad Pro running djay Pro and
我有一个iPad运行djay Pro和Pro
this external mixer,
这个外部混合器,
I'm gonna go ahead and throw on my headphones now,
我要把我的耳机现在,
So, here's the things that's interesting, the external DJ
这是很有趣的事情,外部的DJ
controller acts as an extension of the onscreen UI,
控制器作为扩展屏幕上的用户界面,
And so I can use it to really create kind of a pretty
所以我真的可以使用它来创建一种漂亮
cool performance,
很酷的性能,
Also you're probably wondering what of this can I see,
你可能也想知道我可以看看,
Not much,
不多,
I pretty can see the light coming from the screen and
我可以看到屏幕,发出的光
some of the colorful lights coming from the DJ controller,
一些来自DJ的彩灯控制器,
but that's about it,
但仅此而已,
So knowing that,
所以知道,
we're gonna use VoiceOver to control this interface,
我们将使用画外音来控制这个接口,
Let's go ahead and get the music started,
让我们继续,音乐开始,
Play Okay, so the first thing I'd like to point out is that
玩好了,首先我想指出的是
I have access to information I've never had before,
我获得信息之前,我从来没有,
For example, the time,
例如,时间,
How much time is left on this track?
在这个方向上还剩下多少时间?
Let's find out,
让我们找到答案,
Time deck one, 2:56,
时间甲板1 2:56
That's perfect,
这是完美的,
Okay, so I'm the DJ,
好的,那么我是DJ,
I'm supposed to keep the music going, and
我应该保持音乐,
now I have that kind of information,
现在我有这样的信息,
I also can use these tempo sliders,
我也可以使用这些节奏滑块,
For example if I touch it right now, hold on a second,
例如,如果我现在触摸它,等一会儿,
tempo deck one 0% adjustable,
可调节奏甲板一0%,
So we hear it's at its standard playback speed, but
所以我们听到它的标准播放速度,但是
if I slow it down using the DJ controller and
如果我使用DJ控制器和慢下来
I touch it again,
我又碰它,
Tempo deck one, -7,1%, adjustable,
节奏甲板一7 1%,可调,
We can hear exactly how far I've slown that track down,
我们可以听到究竟多远我slown追踪,
that's really cool,
这是很酷的,
I also can use these multi-dimensional effect pads
我也可以使用这些垫多维效果
for example if I touch it the first time Effects pad,
例如,如果我第一次碰它影响垫,
deck one,
甲板,
But the second time,
但是第二次,
Really cool stuff, right,
很酷的东西,
So between these effects pads, this external controller, and
所以这些影响垫之间,这个外部控制器,和
all this accessible UI,
所有这些访问UI,
I can do a pretty cool performance,
我可以做一个很酷的性能,
So I'd like to go ahead and ask the stage crew to please
所以我想继续,请让舞台工作人员
take VoiceOver off of the PA systems,
休假画外音的PA系统,
So that it's only available to me in my headphones,
所以我只能在我的耳机,
Play deck one,
玩甲板,
Cool, thank you very much,
酷,非常感谢,
And I'm gonna mix for you now,
现在我要为你混合,
Here we go,
我们开始吧,
[MUSIC]
(音乐)
[APPLAUSE] So because of the effort
(掌声)所以,因为工作
that their team put in, people with vision impairments,
他们的团队,有视觉障碍的人,
like Ryan, can DJ just as well as anybody else,
像瑞安,DJ一样别人,
It's something that he loves to do, and it's only possible
他喜欢做的事情,这只是可能
because somebody at that company decided that it was
因为有人在那公司决定
worth it,
值得的,
Thank you,
谢谢你！
[APPLAUSE] For more,
(掌声)更多
please visit us at standford,edu
请访问我们在斯坦福,埃杜